反恐24小时
第九季 第5集
前情提要
你不知道鮑爾對奧德莉做過什麼
You don't know what Bauer did to Audrey.
我陪伴了她三年，讓她康復
I stood by her for three years, and I brought her back.
奥德莉
布德罗
在她有生之年
As long as she lives
她永遠不會聽到傑克·鮑爾這個名字
she'll never hear the name "Jack Bauer."
我的無人機被什麼控制了！
Something's taking control of my drone!
发射
長官，快躲開，快躲開！
Get to cover now! Sir, move! Move!
不！不！
No! No!
鮑爾來過
Bauer's here.
他開槍打傷兩名抗議者
He shot two protestors and forced his way
趁亂進入大使館，他去找過坦納
inside the embassy, and he got to Tanner.
別怕
Don't be afraid.
我是傑克·鮑爾
My name is Jack Bauer.
杰克·鲍尔
控制無人機的技術
The technology that was used
將被人用在
to control our drone is gonna be used in
今天針對平民的大規模恐怖襲擊
a massive terrorist attack against civilians later today.
唐宁街10号
我唯一能阻止恐怖襲擊發生的辦法
The only way that I can stop that attack from happening
來自於你的飛行密鑰
is from the data from your flightkey.
鮑爾被困在美國大使館
Bauer has barricaded himself inside the communications room
內部的通訊室裏
at the American Embassy.
CIA分局局长
史蒂夫·纳瓦罗
我有人質！全都退後！關門！
I've got hostages! Stay back! Close the door now!
誰劫持人質？
Who's taking hostages?
傑克·鮑爾
Jack Bauer.
办公厅主任
马克·布德罗
總統閣下，一個叫德裏克·耶茨的黑客
Mr. President, a hacker by the name of Derek Yates
製造了一台遙控裝置
created an override device which can take
可以控制多達十架美國無人機
control of as many as ten U.S. Drones.
我相信現在此裝置在
Now I believe that the device is in the hands
瑪戈·阿爾哈拉茲手上，她是恐怖分子
of Margot Al-Harazi, a known terrorist.
玛戈·阿尔哈拉兹
昨晚我從惡夢中驚醒
Last night, I woke up from a nightmare
夢見我殺了所有這些人
where I killed all these people.
他說他沒有辦法做這件事
He says he can't go through with it.
西蒙娜·阿尔哈拉兹
你必須操控無人機
You will pilot the drones.
我拒絕，不管你怎樣折磨我
I will not, no matter what you do to me.
我相信你
I believe you.
她的左手
Her left hand.
不要！不要！
No! No!
動手吧！
Do it!
士兵們馬上就會進來
Those Marines are gonna come through that door
他們會殺了你
and they're gonna kill you.
你把飛行密鑰給我
You can give me the flightkey
我幫你完成上傳，帶鑰匙出去
and I can finish the upload for you and get it out of here.
特工
凯特·摩根
我為什麼要相信你？
Why the hell should I trust you?
因為我相信你
Because I really do believe you.
別開槍！我已控制住鮑爾！
Do not fire! I have Bauer in my custody!
現在中情局接管了
This is a CIA matter now.
以下事件发生在
下午15:00 至下午16:00 之间
-=TLF字幕组=-
荣誉出品
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
翻译  筱宸葭
基弗
萨瑟兰
翻译  不再的华年
翻译  lady5bird
时间轴  筱宸葭
伊冯娜·斯特拉霍夫
你無權干涉這次行動
You had no right to interfere with this operation.
校对  诸星龟龟
特效  筱宸葭
大使館是我的管轄區，不是中情局
This embassy is under my jurisdiction, not the CIA's.
泰特·多诺万
要不是我插手，鮑爾已經死了
If I hadn't stepped in, Bauer would be dead.
他該死，那個混蛋向我兩個手下開槍
Well, he should be. Son of a bitch shot two of my men.
玛丽·莱恩·莱杰斯库
他無意傷害他們
And he managed not to wound either of them.
他並非要傷人，而是阻止恐怖襲擊
He is not trying to hurt anyone. He's trying to stop an attack.
威廉·德韦恩
留著向你的上級說吧，摩根特工
Save that for your superiors, Agent Morgan
我會向上級反映
because this is going up the chain
你也最好收拾東西離開
and you might as well start clearing out your desk.
反正今天也不是第一次了
Yeah, well, it's not gonna be the first time today.
格本加·阿金纳格贝
長官，搜過了，飛行密鑰不在他身上
Sir, Bauer's clean. The flightkey isn't on him.
贾尔斯·马特蒂
你等著
You stay right here.
在哪？
Where is it?
迈克尔·温科特
鮑爾，你從證物袋拿走了飛行密鑰
Bauer, you took it from the evidence pouch.
你跟總統說你在下載裏面的數據
You told the president you were trying to download it.
快說東西在哪
Tell me where it is.
本杰明·布拉特
你知道他藏哪了嗎？
You know where he put it?
不知道，一定是剛才你們行動中弄丟了
No. It must have got lost during your little battle charge.
帶她離開！
Get her out of here!
我認識路
I know the way.
這是鮑爾的武器
It's Bauer's weapon.
基姆·瑞弗
奧布賴恩，我是摩根特工，能聽到嗎？
O'Brian, this is Agent Morgan. Do you copy?
客 串
米歇尔·费尔利
科林·萨尔蒙
埃米莉·伯林顿
亚历克·纽曼
能，我聽到你和傑克的對話了，他沒事吧？
Yes. I heard everything you said to Jack. Is he okay?
沒事，不過他現在被陸戰隊的人控制了
Yeah, but he's in custody. He's with the Marines right now.
至少他還活著
Well, at least he's alive.
聽著，飛行密鑰在我手上
Listen, I have the flightkey.
萨夏·达万
乔瑟夫·米尔森
米兰达·雷森
我怎麼把其餘的數據給你？
What do you need me to do to get you the rest of this data?
找台有4G網絡的電腦
Get to a computer with a 4G network
斯蒂芬·弗雷
我會告訴你該怎麼做
I'll walk you through the rest.
剪 辑
乔·霍贝克
知道了，找到電腦後我會打給你
Okay, copy that. I'll call you when I'm ready.
想不到你竟然沒受傷
I can't believe you're in one piece.
到底怎麼回事？
What the hell happened in there?
艺 术 指 导
乔纳森·李
我設法阻止他們殺鮑爾
I managed to stop them from killing Bauer.
摄 影
杰弗里 C·麦咖特
反對無人機！反對無人機！
No more drones! No more drones!
音 乐
肖恩·卡勒里
反對無人機！反對無人機！
No more drones! No more drones!
制作人
金相圭
反對無人機！反對無人機！
No more drones! No more drones!
你還相信鮑爾這麼做是為了阻止恐怖襲擊？
You still think Bauer did all this to stop a terrorist attack?
制 作 人
伊恩·史密斯
是的，假如瑪戈·阿爾哈拉茲真有
Yes. And if Margot Al-Harazi really has the technology
控制美軍無人機的技術，那麼我們得抓緊時間
to steal ten U.S. Drones, then we have to move fast
否則會有很多人喪生
or a lot of people are going to die.
假設你是對的，我們該怎麼辦？
Assuming you're right, what are we going to do about it?
根本沒人相信
Nobody believes this is happening.
所以我們必須找到證據
That's why we have to find proof
證明坦納的無人機被劫持了
that Tanner's drone was hijacked.
用這個
Using this.
坦納的飛行密鑰？你偷來的？
Tanner's flightkey? Tell me you didn't steal it.
鮑爾給我的，陸戰隊的人進來前他沒法把數據
Bauer gave it to me. He wasn't able to finish uploading it
上傳完成給奧布賴恩
to O'Brian before the Marines came in.
克羅伊·奧布賴恩？
Chloe O'Brian?
沒錯，鮑爾讓她
Yes. He's using her
分析飛行密鑰的數據
to analyze the flightkey data.
瘋了
This is crazy.
假如我們不阻止這次襲擊
Well, things are about to get a lot crazier
事情會更加瘋狂，快走吧
if we don't stop this attack, so let's move.
监 制
布莱恩·格雷泽
基弗·萨瑟兰
监 制
强·卡萨
大卫·弗瑞
奧布賴恩，我找到電腦了
Okay, O'Brian, I'm at a computer.
监 制
罗伯特·科克伦
好的，把飛行密鑰插入USB接口
Okay, insert the flightkey into the USB port.
插好了，然後呢
It's done. Go ahead.
加密程序
The encryption program will
會自動恢復鏈接
automatically restore the link
繼續上傳
and resume the upload.
行了，開始繼續上傳了
Okay, it's uploading again.
监 制
曼尼·科托
還有兩分鐘上傳完成
Two minutes before we get it all.
之後還要多久你能找到證據
How long after that before you find proof
證明無人機被劫持？
that the drone was hijacked?
监 制
伊万·卡茨
我不保證能找到證據
I don't know for sure that we will get it
监 制
霍华德·高登
如果找到了，你能把證據給合適的人嗎？
but if we do, will you be able to get it to the right people?
這個不用擔心
Yeah, don't worry about that.
编 剧
乔尔·苏尔诺  罗伯特·科克伦
你只需找到說服其他人
Just get me what I need to convince people
相信這次襲擊會發生的證據，剩下的交給我
that this attack is going to happen, and I'll do the rest.
编 剧
金相圭
帕特里克·萨默维尔
导 演
奥马尔· 马德哈
我知道你很痛苦
I know you're in pain
你想不通
and I know you're confused.
但是我想告訴你的是
But the one thing I don't want you to do
你不用自責
is blame yourself.
這不怪你
This was not your fault.
怪我
It was mine.
要是我早點發現你丈夫的計劃
If I'd known what your husband was planning
我會早點採取措施
I would have acted sooner
事情就不會這樣了
and this wouldn't have been necessary.
原諒我
Forgive me.
她怎麼樣？
How is she?
她會康復的
She'll recover
沒你什麼事
no thanks to you.
一個母親萬萬不該看到自己的女兒
A mother should never have to see her daughter
經歷這種痛苦
go through something like that.
求你別再傷害她
Just please don't hurt her again.
我會照你的吩咐做
I'll do whatever you want.
我知道你會的
I know you will.
怎麼樣了？
Where are we?
目前為止，我已經與四架無人機
So far, I've set up data-links
建立了連接
with four of the drones.
一旦十架都連上
Once all ten are listening
我們會傳輸控制代碼
we'll transmit the override code.
還要多久我們能操控？
When will they be ours?
5分鐘
Five minutes.
如果你要贖罪的話，納維德
If there is any kind of redemption for you, Naveed
現在是時候了
it begins now.
飛行密鑰數據分析已經過半
We're more than halfway through this flightkey data.
我還是沒有發現可疑之處，克羅伊
I still don't see anything suspicious, Chloe.
那就仔細點，傑克是因為你再次入獄
Well, look harder. Jack's headed back to jail because of you.
這點我明白
Yes, I'm aware of that.
你不用一直提醒我
You don't need to keep reminding me.
我就是要
Yes, I do.
你下半輩子每一天我都會提醒你
I'm thinking every day for the rest of your life.
返回，返回
Go back. Go back.
停，這裏
Stop. There.
不錯啊，耶茨
Well done, Yates.
什麼？
What?
你沒看出來？
You don't see it?
我要是看出來就不會問你了
If I saw it, I wouldn't have said "What?"
他把控制代碼分別
What he's done is he's split the override code
插入這些不相連的程序段裏
into these discreet segments here
然後把它們
and he's embedded them
嵌入在無人機收發信號中
in the drone's transponder signal.
幾乎不會被發現，除非是我
Almost impossible to spot...unless you're me.
這就是你要的控制代碼
There's your override code.
摩根特工？
Agent Morgan?
請說
Go ahead.
我們找到控制代碼了
We've got the override code.
這可以證明坦納的無人機是被劫持的
This proves that Tanner's drone was hijacked.
你確定？
Are you sure?
是的，確定
Yes, I'm sure.
我正在截屏
I'm making the screengrabs now.
我把控制代碼高亮顯示了，任何像樣的程序員
I'm highlighting them so any decent programmer
都會明白這些代碼的含義
will be able to understand what he's looking at.
好，發到我手機上
Okay, forward them to my phone.
發了
On it.
他們有發現？
They get something?
等下就知道了
We're about to find out.
裏德
Reed.
喬丹，是我
Jordan, it's me.
你沒事吧？
Are you all right?
沒事，讓納瓦羅聽電話，有東西給你們看
Yeah. Put Navarro on. You both need to see this.
長官，是凱特
Sir, it's Kate.
凱特，你在哪？
Kate, where are you?
我和埃裏克在回來的路上
I'm on my way back with Erik.
我剛剛轉發了一些截圖給喬丹
I just forwarded some screengrabs to Jordan's station.
什麼截圖？
Screengrabs of what?
坦納的無人機的飛行密鑰數據
Data off of Tanner's flightkey from his drone.
收到
Got 'em.
好的，是什麼
Okay, tell me what you see.
看上去是控制代碼
Looks like an override code.
這是什麼？
What is that? What are
出什麼事了？
we talking about here?
史蒂夫，這是
Steve, this is proof
瑪戈·阿爾哈拉茲劫持坦納的無人機
that Margot Al-Harazi commandeered Tanner's drone
殺害那些士兵的證據
and used it to kill those soldiers.
喔，喔，別急，你確定嗎？
Whoa, whoa, slow down. Are you sure?
確定，也就是說還會再有一次襲擊
Yes, which means there's going to be another attack.
史蒂夫，你得向總統示警
Steve, you have got to alert the president.
稍等下，聽我說
Hold on. Listen to me.
我把身家都賭在這上面了
I am putting my ass on the line.
你一定要百分之百確定
You can't have any doubts about this.
是的
I am.
我確定，坦納的無人機確係被人劫持
I'm sure. Tanner's drone was hacked.
瑪麗安娜
Mariana
給我接海勒總統
get me President Heller.
是的，長官
Yes, sir.
美国驻伦敦大使馆现已安全
根據國防部的記錄
According to Department of Defense Records
確定沒問題了，先生
It's confirmed, sir.
大使館現在已經安全了，人質也都無恙
The embassy is now secure, and the hostages are safe.
你確定傑克也好好的？
And you're sure Jack's okay?
是的，他已經被收監
Yes. He's been taken into custody.
我是布德羅
Boudreau.
我是特工納瓦羅，我需要
This is Agent Navarro. I need to speak
和總統通話，是關於傑克·鮑爾的事
to the president. It concerns Jack Bauer.
出什麼事了？
What's going on?
我希望能直接和總統通話，事情緊急
I'd prefer to tell the president directly. It's urgent.
總統閣下，特工納瓦羅
Mr. President, Agent Navarro
要求和您通話，他說事情緊急
on the line. He says it's urgent.
開功放
Put him on your speaker.
你現在可以和總統講話了
You're on with the president.
說吧，納瓦羅
Go ahead, Navarro.
總統閣下
Mr. President
我們有個外勤特工，凱特·摩根
one of my field operatives, Kate Morgan
剛剛收到一份證據，能夠證明
has just recovered evidence that corroborates
傑克·鮑爾不久前和您說過的話
what Jack Bauer told you moments ago.
你再說一遍
Say that again.
先生，您最好能直接聽她說一下這事
Sir, it's best if you hear it from her.
凱特？
Kate?
總統閣下
Mr. President
今早的無人機襲擊事件
the drone attack this morning was in fact
實際上是瑪戈·阿爾哈拉茲精心策劃的一次恐怖襲擊
a terrorist strike orchestrated by Margot Al-Harazi.
她現在掌握了一種設備，能夠
She's in possession of a device that can override
置換我們無人機艦隊的控制系統和命令系統
our drone fleet's control and command systems
而且她打算使用這個設備
and she intends on using it again
再製造一系列後續的襲擊
to launch a series of further attacks.
你怎麼…你怎麼知道的？
How do you... How do you know this?
從坦納的飛行密鑰中恢復的數據可以證明
Data recovered from Tanner's flightkey.
我們的數據分析師
Our data analyst
已經看過了這個證據並驗證了它的真實性
has reviewed the evidence and believes it to be genuine.
我也支持該評估結果
I stand by his assessment.
恕我直言，我們需要親自進行評估
With all respect, we'll need to make our own
總統閣下，傑克·鮑爾說的是實話
assessment. Mr. President, Jack Bauer was telling the truth.
我們需要馬上採取行動，不然很多人
We need to take immediate action or a lot of people
都要丟掉性命
are going to die.
停飛無人機，將軍，停飛全世界的所有無人機
Ground the drones, General. All of 'em, worldwide.
執行，階段四，無人機召回
Execute. Stage 4 UAV recall.
密碼：A，E，C
Code Alpha, Echo, Charlie.
他們在改變航向
They're altering course.
有人知道我們的行動了，馬上發送置換碼
Someone knows what we're doing. Transmit the override.
但是我們的聯繫還沒有全部建立起來
But we haven't completed all the links.
這樣你得不到十架無人機的
You won't get all ten drones.
你沒聽到我的話嗎？
Didn't you hear what I said?
不要考驗我的耐心，納維德
Don't test my patience, Naveed.
無人機在回應了，先生
They're responding, sir.
好
Good.
總統閣下，我們停飛所有無人機的話
Mr. President, with our drone fleet on the ground.
現在不說這個，將軍，我們一件事一件事地來，好嗎？
Not now, General. Let's do one thing at a time. Yeah?
將軍？
General?
歐洲指揮總部，實時信息更新
EUCOM Actual. Update.
你們在重新啟動無人機嗎？
Are you retransmitting?
第七艦載機聯隊的一架無人機
One of the drones from Carrier Air Wing Seven
失去反應了，先生
is not responding, sir.
又出現一架
There's another one.
又一架，怎麼回事，將軍？
And another one. What's going on, General?
講話
Talk to me.
將軍？
General?
他們正在全力應對，總統先生
They're doing everything they can, Mr. President.
有六架無人機沒反應了
Six of the drones are no longer responding.
我們和它們失聯了，先生
We've lost them, sir.
先生，失聯的無人機是RQ-29先鋒號
Sir, the missing drones are RQ-29 Vanguards.
它們是先攻武器，用於摧毀防空設施
They're a first strike weapon, used to take out air defenses.
直接跟我說它們能造成多大破壞
Just tell me how much damage they can do.
它們每一架都裝載有
They each carry a payload
六枚激光制導導彈，這些導彈
of six laser-guided missiles, most of which
大部分都能摧毀半個城市街區
could take out half a city block.
如果發射到公共場所，辦公大樓
If used on a public space, office blocks
學校等地方，傷亡人數可能高達上萬人
schools... casualties could run into the tens of thousands.
而如果
And if a nuclear
以核能發電站為目標
power facility is targeted
傷亡數字還會翻十倍
that number increases tenfold.
這些無人機開往哪裏
Do we have any idea
我們有線索嗎？
where the drones are headed?
根據最後的幾個航向指示
Based on the last vectors
很有可能是開往這裏
the majority appear to be headed here.
倫敦
Toward London.
它們可以在一個小時之內
They could begin entering
進入英國領空
British airspace within an hour.
我們能在它們到達這裏之前
Can't we shoot them down
把它們打下來嗎？
before they get here?
先鋒號裝備有
The Vanguards are equipped with
最先進的隱形技術
the latest in stealth technology
和現有最完備的防護系統
the most advanced protective system ever developed.
雷達無法探測到它們
They cannot be tracked by radar
而且它們也沒有任何紅外特徵
and they have no infrared signature.
也就是說
So what you're telling me is that
我們造出來的飛機連我們自己也偵查不到
we've created an aircraft that can't be detected
為對付它們，我們已經全力壓上
even by us. We're throwing everything we've got at them.
裝有機載預警和控制系統支持的戰鬥機群
Fighter groups equipped with AWACS support
已經升空待命，宙斯盾戰艦
are already in the air, AEGIS ships
也正在開往該區域
are being vectored to the area.
萬不得已時，我們將要依靠目視判定
If necessary, we'll fall back on visual confirmation
但是該區域有70萬立方英里
but since we're talking 700,000 cubic miles
他媽的
Damn it.
我要跟鮑爾談談
I want to talk to Bauer.
看看他對於這些事還知道些什麼
Let's find out what else he knows about all of this.
他已經在過來的路上了
He's already on his way.
我覺得您可能想要跟他談談
I assumed you'd want to talk to him.
他馬上就到
He'll be here any minute.
好
Good.
我之前和鮑爾爭執
I argued against Bauer.
我有責任
I... I feel responsible.
現在不是說這個的時候，馬克
Not now, Mark.
當時的情況你我都瞭解
We're both operating from the same set of facts.
現在我們要做的是，就英國所要面對的事情
What we have to do is we have to warn
向他們示警
the British of what they're facing.
我這就安排和首相的會議
I'll set up a meeting with the prime minister.
知道的人要越少越好
Keep it as small a circle as possible.
是
Yeah.
不好意思，先生
Excuse me, sir.
奧德莉
Audrey.
你是對的，我
You were right. I
我並沒有就事論事
I wasn't arguing the facts.
我對鮑爾的個人看法
I... I let my personal feelings
影響了我的判斷
about Bauer cloud my judgment.
我讓你父親失望了
And I let your father down.
馬克，我…
Mark, I...
我知道，某種程度上，你還是想要保護我
I know, in some ways, you-you were still trying to protect me.
你不能把發生的這些事怪到自己身上
You can't blame yourself for what happened.
我父親需要你，馬克
My father needs you, Mark.
現在他比任何時候都需要你
Now, more than ever.
我必須得去安排這個會了，對不起
I'm, I... I've got to go set up this meeting. I'm sorry.
通缉令
玛戈·阿尔哈拉兹
我們認為這些無人機
We believe these drones were hijacked
遭到了瑪戈·阿爾哈拉茲的劫持
by Margot Al-Harazi and that she
而她現在就在這個國家的某個地方
is somewhere inside this country
可能夥同她的兒子和女兒正在工作
probably working with her son and her daughter.
我們需要盡快找到這些人
We need to find these people and fast.
所以大家回去聯繫自己所有能聯繫到的資源
So go back into your sources, no matter how cold
將這些外國線人和跨部門數據網格一一對應起來
correlate with foreign intel and interagency data grids.
簡報包會很快發到各位的收件箱
Briefing packets will be in your inboxes shortly.
大家動起來
Get up to speed.
歡迎回來
Welcome back.
我得開始
Uh, I'm gonna start
重新面試一下我們在倫敦的所有人員
re-interviewing our London assets.
我知道這樣做機會不大，但是…
I know it's a long shot, but...
我們得談談
We need to talk.
怎麼了？
Uh, what's going on?
凱特，呃
Kate, um.
我必須得把你從執勤人員表中除名
I have to take you off the roster.
別啊
Come on.
大使館陸戰分遣隊的柯迪羅上尉
Captain Cordero with the embassy marine detachment
投訴了你在僵持過程中的行為
he filed a complaint about your actions during the standoff.
投訴狀發回到分區裏，他們不明白
It got back to division, who couldn't understand
為什麼一個已經被轉移到國內的特工
why an agent who had already been
還在執外勤
transferred stateside was still in the field.
我希望你跟他們做出解釋了
Well, I hope you explained it to them.
我努力過了，相信我
I tried, believe me.
我跟他們辯稱你的參與
I argued that your involvement
已經很大程度上減輕了當前的威脅
had already mitigated the current threat.
我來給他們的人打電話
Well, let me call someone at division
你只會是白費唇舌
You'd be wasting your breath.
結束了
It's over.
你要回到你的辦公室去
You need to go back into your office
填一份行動後報告
and fill out an after action report.
凱特，你需要證明的東西你已經證明了
Kate, you proved what you needed to prove.
我需要證明什麼？
What did I need to prove?
我知道這一切是關於亞當的
I know that this was about Adam.
是關於你想找到一種方式來為你丈夫對抗國家的所作所為
About you somehow trying to find a way to make up for what
從某種程度上做出補償
your husband did against this country.
你要為你今天所完成的工作感到開心
Feel good about what you accomplished today.
凱特
Kate.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
這一切都會過去的
You're going to get through this.
我保證
I promise.
長官
Sir.
什麼事？
What is it?
你得來看看這個
You need to see this.
這段視頻剛以匿名形式上傳到跨部門服務器上
This was just posted anonymously on the interagency server.
同時，也發佈在
It's also popping up
聖戰網站
on jihadist Web sites.
兩年前
Two years ago
放上去
Put it up
美國一架無人機
A missile
發射的一枚導彈摧毀了
fired from a U.S. Drone
昆地卡拉的一個會議廳
destroyed a meeting hall in Ghundi Kala.
美國稱其目標是我丈夫
The U.S. Claimed they were targeting my husband
他參與了反抗佔領軍的
who was part of the legitimate struggle
合法鬥爭
against the occupying force
卻被誣陷為恐怖分子
but who they called a terrorist.
美國政府也隱瞞了
What the U.S. Government failed to report
牽連二十三名民眾死亡的事實
was that 23 people were killed
其中包括六名無辜兒童
including six innocent children.
而我能倖存，也是有原因的
I know I was spared for a purpose.
我要求公正處理這名殺人兇手
I demand justice from the man responsible for this slaughter.
詹姆斯·海勒總統
President James Heller.
不像那些敵人，我會在意無辜的生命
Unlike my enemies, I care for the lives of innocents
但若三小時內，海勒總統不到
but unless President Heller surrenders himself to me
我指定的地點來認罪
in three hours at a place of my choosing
上千的倫敦市民
thousands of people in London
將替他而死
will die in his stead.
關於她提的無人機襲擊事件
That drone attack she's talking about
我要對此一切資料
I want everything you have on it.
遵命
Yes, sir.
上千的倫敦市民
thousands of people in London
將替他而死
will die in his stead.
我們還要繼續管這些事麼？
Are we gonna stick around with these things on the way?
不，我們要撤了，但並非因為無人機
No, we're leaving, but not because of the drones.
聽著，鮑爾被抓了
Look, Bauer's in custody.
我們已經盡力做好你們的差事了
We've done everything you've asked us to do.
冒昧問一句，能批准我們離開嗎？
I need to know, will you allow us to leave?
收工
Pack it up.
也許我們還能做更多
There might be more we can do.
克羅伊，罷手吧
Chloe, it's time to go.
會死人的
People are gonna die.
那不該我們管
That's not our fight.
也不是我們的事，就此罷手吧
That's not what we do. It's time to go. Now.
為什麼？
Why?
為什麼？我們跟鮑爾有聯繫
Why? We've been in contact with Bauer
跟中情局有關聯
we've been in contact with the CIA.
我們都算退了一步
Everything's compromised.
你難道忘了政府還在通緝我們？
Have you forgotten the government is still after us?
那些人在黑牢裏是怎麼對你的
Those people who did what they did to you in the black site.
也全都忘了？
Do you remember that?
我沒忘
I remember.
聽著，我知道這樣做對不起鮑爾
Now, look, I know what I did to Bauer was wrong.
但這是在保護我們，我們建立的一切
I was protecting us here, everything we've built.
六年的心血
This is six years.
弊帚自珍，不能白費
It's important. We're not going to lose it.
這是國防部關於瑪戈·阿爾哈拉茲丈夫被殺的
This is the DoD footage of the drone strike
無人機空襲視頻
that killed Margot Al-Harazi's husband.
我們認定這是瑪戈·阿爾哈拉茲
We believe that this is Margot Al-Harazi
她正在爬離廢墟
crawling away from the wreckage.
鬼知道她是怎麼活下來的
God knows how she survived.
這裏還有孩子
There were children there.
她說的是實話
So she was telling the truth.
除了這點，大部分死者都是
Despite her claims, the majority of the people killed
她丈夫手下的激進宗教分子
were members of a radical sect led by her husband.
為何我
Well, why wasn't I told
沒被告知存在平民傷亡？
that there were civilian casualties?
那時我們正忙於無人機計劃的
We were in the middle of a fight to secure funding
資金安保問題
for the drone program.
我們要專注於
We needed to focus
既得目標
on the achieved objective
殺死她的丈夫
which was killing her husband.
於是就隱瞞了這件事？
So you covered it up?
甚至是對我？
Even from me? I thought
我認為這些細節
that the burden of specifics
會讓你從手頭目標上分心
would distract you from the goal at hand.
所以你不願跟我坦白這個事實
So you didn't think that you could trust me with the truth
是因為你怕我一旦知道有平民死亡
that if I knew that we had killed civilians
就會鬆懈對議員的遊說
somehow I wouldn't lobby as hard as you thought.
我是在保護你
I was protecting you.
所以你才僱傭我的
That's why you hired me.
沒有軍事行動
No military action
不會傷及無辜
Is purely surgical.
戰爭一旦打響
And when the fight begins
總有損傷附帶
Collateral damage is always a factor
但無人機計劃
But our U.S. Drone program
能在平民傷亡最少的情況下，給予敵人重擊
lets us hit our enemies with the fewest civilian casualties.
這是你的原話，總統閣下
Those are your words, Mr. President.
是你的信念，如若不然
That's what you believe. And until I hear otherwise
我會不惜代價來執行這條政策
I'm going to do everything I can to further that policy.
爸，也許馬克沒做錯
Dad, maybe Mark made the right call.
不要忘記誰才是敵人
Let's not forget who the enemy is.
我知道敵人是誰
I know who the enemy is.
我們剛成全了他們一次精神的勝利
We've just given our enemy a moral victory.
精神的勝利？
A moral victory?
瑪戈·阿爾哈拉茲從沒考慮過
Margot Al-Harazi does not think for one second
我會去認罪的可能
that I'm gonna give myself up.
一旦規定的三小時過去
When that deadline comes around in three hours
開始向平民投彈時
and she starts bombing civilians, she's going
她會將責任歸咎於我
to be able to blame it on me.
於是，她也得到了世界上半數人的認可
And half the world is going to agree with her.
閣下，鮑爾帶到了
Sir, they're bringing Mr. Bauer now.
謝了
Thank you.
這裏沒事了，下去吧
We're fine. Give us the room.
那我就直說了，傑克
I'm gonna get right to the point, Jack.
我們已經證實瑪戈·阿爾哈拉茲
We've confirmed that Margot Al-Harazi
控制了六架無人機
has six U.S. Drones under her control.
並被認定正均飛往倫敦
We believe they're headed for London.
看來我說對了
So I was right.
她拍攝了一個視頻
She just made a video
說如果我找她認罪
in which she said she would forgo the attacks
她便放棄襲擊
if I would surrender to her
前提是三小時內
within three hours.
你有任何可以幫助我們
Is there anything that you can tell me
逮捕她的線索麼？
that will help us catch her?
有一個
There is a man
地下軍火商
an underground arms dealer.
他與阿爾哈拉茲有多年生意往來
He's done business with Al-Harazi for years.
她信任這個人
She trusts him.
即使現在，我仍覺得這個人能聯繫到她
Even now, I still think he can contact her.
告訴我們他叫什麼，我們去找他
Give us his name and we'll pick him up.
閣下，這人可蹲過世界上最差的幾個監獄
Sir, this man has done time in some of the worst prisons
因為他從不開口
in the world. Because he didn't talk.
即使你活捉了他，你也不能
Even if you captured him alive, you wouldn't be able
趕在襲擊發生前撬開他的嘴
to break him in time to stop these attacks from happening.
要想得到線索，最好還是讓我
The best way for us to get the information you need
重新跟他取得聯繫
is for me to reestablish contact with him
再暗中獲得情報
and try and acquire it by stealth.
你想我放你回去？
You want me to put you back in the field?
直到抓住她，是的
Until she's captured, yes.
這可難辦，傑克
That's a big ask, Jack
即使是在這種情況下
even under the circumstances.
俄方還在吵著要你命
The Russians are still crying for your head.
要是發現我們抓了你後，又把你放了
They find out that we have you and then we let you go
那我的麻煩可比現在大得多
I'll have a larger crisis than I have now.
總統閣下，我向您保證
Mr. President, I give you my word
一旦危機解除
that I will surrender myself to the authorities
我就向當局自首
as soon as the threat has been neutralized.
我做不到，傑克
I can't do it, Jack.
告訴我們他的名字和地址
Just give us the guy's name and his location
我們的人會去找他
and our guys will go pick him up.
不行，對不起，閣下
I can't. I'm sorry, sir.
我不會讓您因在意俄方態度
I'm not gonna let you blow the only lead that we've got
而把這唯一的機會白白浪費掉
because you're worried about what the Russians will do.
想抓到瑪戈·阿爾哈拉茲
You want to capture Margot Al-Harazi
就得按我說的做
you're gonna have to do it my way.
傑克，你流亡了四年
You've been in exile for four years, Jack.
還是不開竅麼？
Haven't you learned anything?
總統閣下，希望您考慮我的請求
Mr. President, I hope you consider my request.
趁著還不晚
While you still have time.
閣下，我奉命通知您
Sir, I was asked to let you know
首相已經在路上了
that the prime minister is on his way.
再考慮下，傑克
Think about it, Jack.
時間還趕得上嗎？
Are we still on schedule?
第一架無人機十四分鐘後到達倫敦
The first drone will reach London in 14 minutes.
伦敦
很好
Good.
我要見西蒙娜
I want to see Simone.
為什麼？
Why?
我只想陪陪她，瑪戈
I just want to be with her, Margot.
我是她丈夫，我愛她
I'm her husband and I love her.
拜託
Please.
時間不多了
We have a little time.
伊恩可以監視飛行路徑
Ian can monitor the flight paths.
行
It's all right.
去吧
Go.
嘿
Hey.
讓我看看
Let me have a look.
你需要看醫生
You need to get to a doctor.
我從沒想過我媽會這樣
I never thought my mother would go this far.
你媽發佈的那個視頻
The video that your mother sent out
我做了手腳，可被定位追蹤
...I made sure it was traceable.
我在我們房間裏藏了證據
And I've hidden evidence in our room that will prove what I did.
就在地板下
Under the floorboards.
當局一到，我會聲稱
When the authorities arrive, I will claim
你從開始就反對襲擊
that you've been opposed to this attack from the start
是強行被控制在這的
and that you've been held here against your will.
記住了麼？
Remember that, okay?
我愛你，西蒙娜
I love you, Simone.
我保證
I promise.
沒事的，我保證這一切都會過去，好麼？
all right? I promise I will get you through this, okay?
快點
Gear up.
怎麼了？
What's going on?
阿爾哈拉茲錄影中發現可能蹤跡
A possible hit on the Al-Harazi tape.
有新線索嗎？
Update?
後門追蹤程序代理不斷改變
The back-trace program was being bounced from proxy to proxy
卻突然放出了個IP地址
but it suddenly spat out an IP address.
不管是我技術夠好還是走了狗屎運
I don't know if I'm really that good or that lucky
我都拿下了
but I'll take it.
好了
Okay.
就是這裏
There it is.
看來是一處大宅子
Looks like a large estate.
瑞特，要隊伍裝備，3分鐘後出發
Ritter, finish prepping the team. We're leaving here in three.
我們出發？
We're leaving?
是的，我也去，我帶隊
Yeah, I'm going with. I'm running point.
有問題嗎？
You have a problem with that?
沒有，長官
No, sir.
很好，我會告知總統我們有線索了
Good. I'll notify the president we have a lead.
大家開始吧
Let's go, people.
沒事的，湯姆
It's okay, Tom.
你不該來這
You shouldn't be here.
我只是
I just.
我只是想告訴你
I just wanted to tell you
我只是…我想告訴你
I just...I wanted to tell you that we have a lead
我們有阿爾哈拉茲藏身處的線索了
on Al-Harazi's location, and
還有
and there's a
已經展開行動了
an operation already in progress.
真是好消息
That's good news.
我甚至都不知道從何說起
I don't even know where to begin.
我也是
Me neither.
你結婚了
You're-you're married.
你幸福嗎？
Are you happy?
他對你好嗎？
Is he good to you?
我知道當我聽說這一切時我應該更多維護你
I know that I should have defended you more when I heard
奧德莉，不
all those things... Audrey, no.
別說了
Stop.
他們說的一切
Everything they said
都是真的
i-is true.
事情很複雜，但是
It was complicated, but
我殺了那些人
I killed those people.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
非常抱歉
I'm so sorry.
你該走了
You should go.
你快走吧
You need to go.
奧德莉，你快走吧
Audrey, you need to go.
現在就走
You need to go now.
走
Now.
謝謝你的到來，阿拉斯泰爾
Thank you for coming, Alastair.
首先，我要向你保證
Well, first of all, I just want to assure you
我們對這段阿爾哈拉茲視頻極為重視
we take these Al-Harazi tapes very seriously.
那太好了
That's good to know.
我們要問的第一個問題當然是
The first question we have to answer, of course
事實上她是否能實施這些威脅
is whether or not she can actually carry out these threats.
她能
She can.
我正想和你說這事
That's what I wanted to talk to you about.
25分鐘前
25 minutes ago
我們和北大西洋上空飛行的
we lost contact with six Vanguard attack drones
六架先鋒號戰鬥無人機失去了聯繫
operating over the North Atlantic.
我們認為如今這些無人機
We now believe that they're under the control
在瑪戈·阿爾哈拉茲的控制之下
of Margot Al-Harazi
她意圖利用它們打擊倫敦範圍內的目標
who intends to use them against targets in London.
我不明白，總統先生
I don't understand, Mr. President.
這怎麼可能？
How is this possible?
我們不清楚她是怎麼弄的
We're in the dark of how she pulled it off.
我們還在調查中
We're still trying to sort that out.
你為迪戈加西亞島的無人機基地尋求我的支持
You asked for my support for the drone base in Diego Garcia.
我給了你支持
I gave you that support
代價是昂貴的政治資本
at the cost of serious political capital.
我知道
I know that.
而這就是你帶給我的消息？
And this is the news you bring me?
那些無人機在恐怖分子的手中？
That those drones are in the hands of a terrorist?
英國公民面臨死亡？
And that British citizens are going to die?
我們祈禱那樣的事不會發生
We pray that's not going to happen.
你要如何阻止這事？
And how are you going to stop it?
我們認為我們已找到阿爾哈拉茲
We think we've located Al-Harazi.
我們的本地分局局長納瓦羅特工
Our local station chief, Agent Navarro, is
會親自帶隊
personally leading a raid
突襲她的藏身處
on where we think she's hiding out.
我們正在建立現場傳送
We're setting up a feed
以便行動展開時
so that we can monitor the operation
我們能同步監測
as it unfolds.
預計八分鐘到達
Your E.T.A. Is eight minutes.
收到，有衛星了嗎？
Copy that. You have satellite yet?
好了
Coming up now.
這次任務該你領隊，而不是納瓦羅
You should be leading this mission, not Navarro.
功勞都會變成他的
He's gonna take the credit when you're the one
而這一切卻是你發現的
who figured out what was going on.
不是的
It's not right.
走開下
Give me a second.
摩根特工？
Agent Morgan?
你看過那段阿爾哈拉茲視頻了嗎？
Have you seen the Al-Harazi tape?
當然了，每個人都看到了
Of course. Everyone's seen it.
網上都是
It's all over the Internet.
有瑪戈藏身處的線索了嗎？
Are you any closer to finding Margot?
呃，我打來就為這事
Uh, that's why I'm calling.
一份視頻復本
A copy of the tape was deposited
放到了我們的跨部門服務器上
onto our interagency server.
我們的數據分析師反追蹤到一個IP地址
And our data analyst was able backtrace it to an IP address.
真的？你應該給他升職加薪
He was? You should give him a raise.
這一切看起來太容易了
Well, something about it just seems too easy.
我同意，她一生致力於
Yeah, I agree. She spends her whole life dedicated to planning
策劃那場襲擊，又怎麼會犯這樣的愚蠢錯誤？
that attack, and then, makes a dumb mistake like this?
我們有一隊人已經行動了
Look, we already have a team on the way, but I was hoping
但是我希望你能看看那段視頻
that you could take a look at the tape.
我得看到原視頻
I'd need to see the original.
也就是說有權訪問你的網絡
That means access to your network.
你不是已經有權限了嗎？
Well, don't you already have access?
我們很能幹，但還沒到那種程度
We're good, but we're not that good.
我可以告訴你如何開啟一個套接字
I can tell you how to open a socket.
在聽嗎？
Are you there?
好吧，詳細說一遍
Okay, walk me through it.
他們不會來了，納維德
They're not coming, Naveed.
我不明白你的意思
I-I don't know what you're talking about.
你是個愚蠢的騙子，納維德
You're a terrible liar, Naveed.
伊恩發現了你在視頻上做的手腳
Ian detected what you did to the video.
你關閉了一個安全緩衝區
You switched off one of the security buffers
以便他們能找到我們
so they could find us.
西蒙娜不知道這事，瑪戈
Simone didn't have anything to do with this, Margot.
請別傷害她
Don't hurt her, please.
西蒙娜再也不會為你贖罪了
Simone will never pay for your sins again.
你還需要我控制無人機
You still need me to pilot the drones.
伊恩學得很快，他一直在觀察你
Ian's a quick learner. He's been watching you.
他覺得自己可以接替
He thinks he can take over.
我們很快會知道答案的
We'll soon find out.
帶他出去
Take him out of here.
美國人應該在大約五分鐘後
The Americans should reach the other house
到達另一處房子
in about five minutes.
沒人能活著出去
No one gets out of there alive.
我會為他們做好準備的
I'll be ready for them.
怎麼了？你在幹什麼？我們要走了
What are you doing? What are you doing? We're leaving.
我跟摩根特工通了話
I spoke with Agent Morgan.
我打算幫她看看那段阿爾哈拉茲視頻
I'm going to help her with the Al-Harazi tape.
克羅伊，幫鮑爾是一回事
Chloe, it was one thing to help Bauer.
我們別無選擇
We had no choice.
我不是加入中情局，但是我要幫她
I'm not joining the CIA, but I am gonna help her
所以我哪也不去
so, I'm not going anywhere.
克羅伊？別這樣
Chloe? Come on.
我必須這麼做，艾德裏安！
Listen, I have to do this. Adrian!
她想留下，她就留下
She wants to stay. She stays.
不關你的事，不是嗎？
It's none of your business, is it?
我知道很多像你這樣的人
I know many people like you.
表裏不一
You act like you are one thing, but you're not.
帶著你的人和電腦離開這
Take your comrades and your computers and go.
我沒法相信你會這麼做
I can't believe you're doing this.
我必須這麼做
I have to do this.
我不希望你走
I don't want you to go.
留下幫幫我吧
Please stay and help me.
我愛你，克羅伊
I love you, Chloe.
好了，我們在現場了
All right, we're on site.
收到，一切安全，可以前進
Copy. You're clear to proceed.
好的，B隊，前往目標
All right, B Team, advance to target.
兩分鐘後到達射擊範圍
Two minutes until we're in firing range.
安全，繼續上樓
Clear. Proceeding upstairs.
最终IP地址
检查IP重定向
警告：检测到IP地址重定向
检查代理名单
走開下
Give me a sec.
說吧
Go ahead.
瑪戈的視頻少了一個安全緩衝區
Margot's tape had a missing security buffer.
我們知道，我們成功追蹤到一個IP地址
Uh, we know. We were able to trace the IP
我們有一隊人現在就在那
to an address. We have a team there right now.
不是，IP地址是錯的，有人插入了一個重定向
No, the IP address is wrong. Someone inserted a redirect.
你們的隊伍正走向一個陷阱
Your team's headed into a trap.
你確定嗎？
Are you sure?
是的，非常確定，我現在正在查看代碼
Yes, I'm sure. I'm staring at the code right now.
史蒂夫，這是陷阱
Steve, it's a set-up.
你必須馬上撤離隊伍
You need to get the team out of there right now.
什麼？再說一遍
What? Say again?
喬丹發現的IP地址是故意放進去的
The IP address that Jordan found was put there on purpose.
你怎麼知道的？
How do you know that?
現在別管這個
Doesn't matter right now.
史蒂夫，你的隊伍處在危險中
Steve, your team is in danger.
馬上離開那裏！
Get out of there right now!
我是納瓦羅，行動取消
This is Navarro. Abort the operation.
重複一遍，行動取消
I repeat, abort the operation.
怎麼回事？他們怎麼撤出了？
What's going on? Why are they pulling out?
準備就位
We're in position.
幹掉他們
Take them.
錢德勒的小隊，他們到底在哪？
Chandler's squad-- where the hell are they?
史蒂夫？
Steve?
史蒂夫？史蒂夫，收到了嗎？
Steve? Steve, do you copy?
埃裏克？
Erik?
史蒂夫？
Steve?
伊恩已經證明了自己，納維德
Ian has proved himself, Naveed.
我想你知道這代表什麼
I think you know what that means.
求求你，瑪戈，別這樣，瑪戈
Please, Margot, don't do this. Margot.
我視你如子
I treated you like a son.
把女兒托付給你
Trusted you with my daughter.
對你信任有加
Put my faith in you.
我沒法這麼做，瑪戈
I couldn't do it, Margot.
我不能謀殺那些人
I couldn't murder all those people.
謀殺？
Murder?
你不懂
You have no idea.
你沒見過自己所愛之人被燒死
You didn't watch the person you love burn to death.
這不能成為
It doesn't justify
這一切的借口，瑪戈
any of this, Margot.
求求你，瑪戈，別殺我
Please, Margot. Margot, don't-don't kill me.
求求你，瑪戈，求你了
Please. Margot, please.
要是你愛西蒙娜
If you love Simone, you have to know
你就該知道她不想你這麼做的
that she wouldn't want you to do this.
問問她
Ask her.
西蒙娜？
Simone?
我想你知道答案了
I think you have your answer.
更多原创翻译字幕请访问
TLF论坛：http://bbs.eastgame.org
TLF中文字幕站：http://sub.eastgame.org
TLF字幕组微博：http://weibo.com/tlfsubs